I buy newspapers every day and I, um, naturally buy the two largest serving newspapers of the city,
我每天都买报纸, 而且我, um, 一般地会买我们市发行量最大的两份报纸，
the Boston Globe and the Boston Herald,
《Boston环球报》和《Boston先驱报》,
but what I truly love are our weekly community newspapers that really focus on the city of Cambridge, which is where I live.
不过我真正喜欢的是我们每周发行一次的社区报, 因为这份报纸的主要内容都是关于剑桥市的消息，而我就住在这个城市。
I mainly go right to the business section and then after that maybe the "metro",
我看报一般都会先直接翻到财经版, 然后也许会看看"都市版",
what I'd like to see, what the indicators are saying, all the smart people are saying,
我喜欢看的, 比如那些统计指标说了什么, 有关行家说了些什么,
just to kind of be in the know, in the flow of the money.
就是去了解行情以及一般的经济动向.
International news, and then I'll go to "metro" news and sports.
我一般先看国际新闻, 然后会翻看"都市版"的新闻和体育动态.
I usually pick up whatever is available, ah, not particular in terms of any brands or anything like that.
我一般有什么报就看什么报, ah, 对报纸名称什么的并不太挑剔.
I travel a lot, so whether it's the Miami Herald or the Chicago Tribune or USA Today, doesn't make that much difference.
我因为经常出门在外, 所以不管是《Miami先驱报》, 《Chicago论坛报》, 还是《今日美国》, 对我来说没太大区别.
I like public radio broadcast, it's, um, good coverage, good explanations of the news,
我喜欢听公共电台的广播, it's, um, 范围较广, 对新闻内容的解释较为令人满意,
facts behind the headlines in greater detail than the newspaper sometimes and ahead of the newspaper too.
有时新闻提要后的具体内容比报纸更为详细, 而且也比报纸更及时.
I think newspapers are the best.
我还是觉得报纸最好.
I think probably on the bottom end of the scale is TV.
如果排队的话, 我觉得电视也许该排在最后.
It's more entertainment.
电视里更多的是娱乐节目.
I listen to a lot of radio and, er, especially the public radio,
我听电台广播听得很多, er, 尤其是公共电台的广播,
er, I like the reporting in depth, that's where I get most of my news and then the TV.
er, 我喜欢有深度的报道, 这是我获得消息的主要来源, 其次就是电视了.
When you pick up newspapers, whether it's, you know, these particular newspapers,
当你拿起报纸的时候, 不管是哪种报纸, you know, 这些报纸,
you would think that we're the only country on this planet.
你会产生这样一种感觉, 我们的国家是这个星球上唯一的国家.
Um, once in a while, you pick up something, um, in Bosnia or whatever,
Um, 偶尔, 你也会看到一点儿, um, 关于Bosnia的消息或其他一些消息,
but, er, for the most part it's very slanted to US.
但是, er, 大多数还是倾向于美国的新闻.